Hey.
You're not treating Eui-ju like that on purpose, are you?
Like what?
She told me she thinks the essay and demerits are unfair.
You're not doing that because of the filming, right?
Me?
You wouldn't, right?
I'm pretty sure that was all just a misunderstanding.
I know she didn't film us.
Then why are you doing it?
Why are you being so strict with just her?
I can't accept her…
only getting four points in math.
Have some breakfast.
I hear after-school classes don't happen unless five kids sign up.
I only have four.
I heard yesterday, Woo-su already has ten.
Oh, you found your glasses.
Took you long enough to notice.
Dude!
What's going on? You found them.
-Where did you find them? -Did someone see your flyer?
How much did you give them?
Why would I give any?
Look at this punk.
The person didn't want a reward.
-What? -Why not?
Who knows?
What a lifesaver.
You should bow to them, dude.
You should express your gratitude to bring more blessings back to yourself.
Yeah, dude, it's the least you can do.
-Otherwise you'll get pooped on again. -Yeah, dude.
CHAPTER 15: BLINK TWICE IF YOU'RE HERE UNDER DURESS
Is it just me or does your heart burst every time Yoon picks up his pen?
Even Si-on's breathing gets me right in the feels.
I wish I could be tied up with that leather watch on Yoon's wrist.
The way that Tae-ha looks at Yoon. Is he for real?
Hi.
What's so funny?
What? Well…
The new thing I uploaded
is causing quite a stir.
Really? Show me.
I can't, it's embarrassing. Sorry.
The way you're being so secretive about it…
Is it R-rated?
No, don't be silly.
It's not like BL, is it?
BL?
Yeah, you know,
men liking other men.
Oh, BL.
I have heard of that.
I don't get people who like that kind of stuff.
Of course.
You're right.
If it's a romance, why pair two guys instead of a guy and a girl?
What's so fun about that?
Right.
The weather's great, isn't it?
Yeah.
What's our first period?
My dad always said…
When faced with a difficult choice…
Is that your application form?
Finally got my fifth person.
This is going to be an elite team.
Let's do this, rising star of the athletic world!
Sorry, Mr. Jung.
Taking the more difficult path…
is the way to salvation.
Mr. Jung, I really wanted to do after-school PE.
But something came up.
Blink twice if you're here under duress.
She has a passion for math.
She wants to get her score up so I couldn't just say no.
-Me? -She should do what she's good at.
Her long-distance running is right up there.
She obviously isn't an athletic type, is she?
Her face has got lazy written all over it.
Me?
No, it doesn't.
I'm really hard-working.
How much do you sleep?
Ten hours.
As long as you focus when you're awake.
What rank are your grades?
Ninth.
Listen to your homeroom teacher.
But, sir.
They're not all nine.
Today we're going to study the poem
Invocation by Kim So-wol.
INVOCATION
KIM SO-WOL
Let me read it aloud first.
"A name which was shattered into pieces."
Why doesn't Dong-ju use the present I gave him?
He probably doesn't want to burden you.
If he uses it, you might feel obliged to get him something else.
Do you think?
I'm going to tell him I like him as soon as I turn 20.
You really think you'll still like him until then?
You've never even lasted 200 days before.
This time it's different.
I'm really curious.
Why do you like Mr. Yoon?
Like what specifically?
Not his looks. There must be something special.
Dong-ju
is different.
How is he different?
Compared to all the other guys you dated.
I feel sorry for him.
What?
I don't know.
Just looking at his face
makes me sad.
It makes my heart ache.
I guess.
My mom said she married my dad because she felt sorry for him.
She also said never to marry someone out of pity.
That plenty of people ruined their lives like that.
But if you really like someone,
I guess that's what it feels like.
-Right? -Yes.
Feeling sorry for someone for no reason?
I'm on cleaning duty again.
-Good afternoon. -Good afternoon.
Great work today.
Just look at that face.
Who's ever going to feel sorry for him?
Those on cleaning duty, make sure you do it.
No one, whatsoever. For the rest of his life!
Dismissed.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
I can't say I'm surprised, but he's a real freak.
He hits you with demerits on a whim.
And now after-school math too.
He's the devil.
Let's do it together.
I'd follow you to hell.
But after-school math? No.
Punishing someone with what they hate most.
Honestly, it's genius. Right?
Hey, girls.
Do you have plans?
-Not really. -Nope.
Why?
I have detention cleaning and then after-school class.
Why do you ask?
There's something I want to do now that I'm in Korea.
-What? -What is it?
What is it?
CHAPTER 16: MATH IS ABOUT PERSEVERANCE
Mr. Jung.
I guess all I can do is gaze on you from afar.
Is this unbearable pain in my heart
because of a love that can never be?
Why is fate so cruel to us?
What are you doing here? Do you have something to tell me?
Mr. Ga forced you, right?
Gosh.
No.
Let me help you.
Don't worry about it.
There's no need.
Oh, come on.
I said it's fine.
Thanks.
I'm not saying this for the sake of it.
You're really talented.
So feel free to ask me anything.
If you need anything, just tell me.
Okay.
So…
You competed in the singles luge
until you were forced to retire after fracturing your left shin.
How did you know that?
I read a news article about it.
It doesn't affect my daily life.
But you were forced to retire after finishing fourth at the Winter Games.
You must have a lot of regrets.
Are you asking
if I regret not having won a medal?
There's something more important than that.
As I watched the medalists from below the podium,
I realized something.
Despite all the sweat I shed to compete in the Games, they must have shed more.
I thought I was going to die.
They must have felt the same, right?
In that moment, my placing no longer mattered.
And above all,
I'd kept my promise to myself.
I never gave up.
That's what counts.
If I'd done after-school PE,
we could have talked all the time and gotten close.
If it wasn't for Mr. Ga…
-Hello? -Where are you?
Come to my office and get the printouts for the class.
Can't you get someone else to do it?
I'm sure Ha-su would love to.
But you're the TA for this after-school class.
Since when?
You've got three minutes.
Mr. Jung, I need to go.
-You're leaving? -Yes.
Goodbye.
She's top of class one.
And she's top of class three.
This class is the best of the best.
I don't belong here at all.
Are you here to bring us these?
No, I'm taking this class too.
You? Why?
Mr. Ga told me I should.
Mr. Ga?
It's probably so we don't waste our time.
It's better she does all that.
Do you think?
I guess.
She got four points in the September mock exam.
Four points?
Where are you going?
Mr. Ga.
Can't you just let me go?
I'm too bad at math to be in this class.
My old tutor and my cousin both told me
I don't have a head for math. I think they were right.
I'm totally hopeless with numbers.
Unlike subjects you can memorize,
more effort doesn't always mean better scores.
Those four points.
How did you get them? Did you just guess?
No, I solved them.
There you go!
When Gauss estimated the number of primes,
he spent years manually calculating every single prime up to three million.
Math is about perseverance, and you have it in spades.
So get back in there.
But…
Since angle CFA
is equal to angle CAF,
AC equals CF, which is 14.
Now try and solve it.
What the heck? Why is she putting lip tint on?
And during class at that.
No way!
Wow!
I know they say birds of a feather and all.
Does she like Mr. Ga? Amazing!
When am I going to write episode three?
Yeo Eui-ju!
Yes, sir!
Yes.
Aren't you going to write episode three?
Episode three?
Yes.
Explain how it goes.
Readers will probably expect
Yoon to pay back the ten million won in episode three,
but the highlight of episode three is the swoon-inducing scene
between Si-on and Yoon.
They're studying together at Si-on's place,
when Si-on says to Yoon,
"You're really bad."
"You keep making me think bad thoughts."
Yoon replies,
"Stop messing around."
To which Si-on responds,
"Do I look like I'm joking?"
"I've never once joked with you!"
…joked with you.
Do the problems we covered in class today and hand them in tomorrow.
By tomorrow? How am I supposed…
Damn it.
CHAPTER 17: JMT! (JUST A MARVELOUS TEACHER)
There's something I want to do now that I'm in Korea!
GUESTHOUSE
A pajama party!
-Eui-ju! -It's Eui-ju!
Where have you been?
Why are you so late?
Is this the famous shaman's place?
Be seated.
How did you come to be here?
-Is your name Yeo Eui-ju? -Verily.
Hello.
-What took you so long? -You're so late!
Got you a present. Welcome!
Oh, Eui-ju.
So sweet!
That's so cute!
-Where's mine? -It's really cute.
-It's really cute. -Thank you.
Wow, you ate all this?
-It's nothing. -I'm bursting.
Thus doth Kim Dan-ji proclaim.
Eat like there's no tomorrow!
I'm so full.
What is that?
Yeah! Now it's a party.
-That's a must. -Of course!
Let me just make some space.
-We always have a space for dessert! -Rice cake sticks!
Sweet potato.
Let's go to the kitchen.
Go to the kitchen!
Let's go!
Put this on before we go.
This?
Jenny, well done.
Put them like this.
And roast them.
I'll show you the proper taste of Korea.
I can't wait.
Looks good, right?
Yes.
-It's really warm. -It is, right?
What? Do you need something?
So…
Hey, Jenny, by any chance,
do you know A Night in Paris?
A NIGHT IN PARIS
You know that novel?
Yeah, it used to be my favorite.
The female protagonist, Isabelle, meets her Brazilian boyfriend in Paris.
At the Louvre.
I did a double take when I saw your messenger username.
But what you told us about how he asked you out was the same.
So you knew all along.
That I lied.
Don't worry about it.
Everyone wants to be the star of their own novel.
I just assumed you really like that novel.
I don't really have a boyfriend.
Everything I know about love I learned from books.
It's fine.
It's no big deal.
-Really? -Yeah.
I read it in translation first.
And I really wanted to read the original.
That's why I started learning Korean.
You speak Korean this well after learning from a novel?
I read it so often I practically memorized it.
Do you like to read romance novels too?
Well, you know.
I started off by reading modern romances.
Then I switched to foreign romantic fantasy.
And after that…
And after that?
Anyhow.
Modern romance is the most mainstream.
Right.
I fell in love with Korea after reading Korean romance web novels.
Oh, I see.
Which other novels did you enjoy?
Fifty Shades of Mr. CEO. Have you heard of it?
-Of course! Have you read it? -Yes!
Did you read it too?
-You did a great job. -Looking good.
-Hey, this rice cake is amazing. -Stop it.
You cooked these perfectly.
Right? Have a bite.
Oh, not yet.
-Yeah, you need to add some kimchi. -Sweet potatoes…
-Kimchi? -Yes, put it on top…
How is it?
-Wow! -Isn't it great?
Just marvelously tasty!
You've got something on your face.
-You've got something here as well. -Come here.
-Hey! -No, I don't.
Jenny, too.
Hey!
-With some grain syrup. -Honey.
-It's honey. -Try it.
It's good, right?
-Do you like it? -Isn't it great?
This is just marvelously tasty too!
This is nice.
Man, I'm so full.
Look at all those stars.
There are so many of us, right?
Like Mr. Ga said.
We're all stars in the universe.
When he says things like that, doesn't he sound like the Little Prince?
Know what I mean?
Somewhere in the sky, one of those shining stars belongs to me.
And that star is speaking to me.
Have you done your homework?
-No! -What is it?
My math homework!
No, my math homework.
I couldn't even hang out properly because of after-school math.
When am I supposed to do my homework?
I hate it.
I hate it so much.
Aren't you going to get more demerits if you don't do it?
-She's right. -Whatever.
What are you going to do?
No idea.
No idea, I don't care!
Eui-ju, you've become gutsy.
Did you see his face when she faked being sick?
-I remember. -I know.
He gave her a look of death.
CHAPTER 18: STRANGELY FAMILIAR, ALMOST MATHEMATICAL
Mr. Ga.
I couldn't do the homework.
Can I just write out the solutions ten times each?
Did you even try?
Keep trying until you can solve at least one by yourself.
Like you did on the mock exam.
That only works sometimes.
This isn't one of those times.
Yeo Eui-ju.
Yes, sir?
What did I say math was on my first day?
The universe.
Euclid?
In here, not during class.
I said it's a subject that requires thought.
Yes, sir.
You probably weren't paying attention. Nor are you now.
I thought solving one problem would make you think.
I didn't realize you were such a lost cause.
I'm very disappointed.
I'm sorry.
What on earth was he expecting of me to be so disappointed?
He even made me feel sorry for him.
Still at least, I got some dialogue out of it.
So, how did he pay back the ten million?
You keeping the rest of this juicy story to yourself?
Did she faint while writing?
Give me my episode three!
Episode three!
The lines from Mr. Ga goes…
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOU WERE SUCH…
I'M VERY DISAPPOINTED, YOON
I didn't realize you were such a lost cause.
I'm very disappointed, Yoon.
Why?
How can you read at a time like this?
Stop messing around.
Is Tae-ha gonna be waiting outside your house again?
YOON'S PAUSE INCENSES SI-ON
I don't know.
You're really bad.
You keep making me think bad thoughts.
I love it when you look at me, lying down.
It makes me want to smush my lips against yours.
Until you can't breathe.
SI-ON PRESSED AGAINST YOON, HIS BREATHING RAGGED
Now that's a proper cliffhanger.
There's no way you can skip the next episode.
That smell
isn't one I'm used to in the library.
And yet, it's strangely familiar. How should I put it…
Like a skincare lotion that a jerk would use.
Almost…
mathematical?
I must be mistaken.
Keep calm, Eui-ju.
It's probably nothing.
No, it's nothing.
Move!
Stay right there, Yeo Eui-ju!
I mean,
I.
Muk.
Subtitle: Paul Carver